<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Salesforce to Siebel Account Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
I want to synchronize accounts from Salesforce instance to Oracle Siebel Business Objects.

This template should serve as a foundation for the process of migrating accounts from Salesforce instance to Oracle Siebel Business Objects, being able to specify filtering criteria and desired behavior when an account already exists in the Siebel instance. 

As implemented, this template leverage the [Batch Module](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing).
The batch job is divided to Input, Process and On Complete stages.
During the Input stage the template will query SalesForce for all the existing Accounts that match the filter criteria.
During the Process stage the template will create the accounts in Siebel and update those which already exist.
Finally during the On Complete stage the template will output statistics data into the console and send a notification email with the results of the batch execution to the group of configured email addresses. 
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
<![CDATA[
To make this Anypoint template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered. All of them deal with the preparations in both, that must be made in order for all to run smoothly. **Failling to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="sieb_dst">
		<![CDATA[
In order to make the siebel connector work smoothly you have to provide the correct version of the siebel jars (Siebel.jar, SiebelJI_enu.jar) that works with your Siebel installation.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="run_it">
<![CDATA[
No matter how you run this template, this is an example of the output you'll see after hitting the HTTP endpoint:

<pre>
<h1>Batch Process initiated</h1>
<b>ID:</b>6eea3cc6-7c96-11e3-9a65-55f9f3ae584e<br/>
<b>Records to Be Processed: </b>9<br/>
<b>Start execution on: </b>Tue Oct 13 10:05:33 GMT-03:00 2015
</pre>
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_cloudhub">
<![CDATA[
Once your app is all set and started, supposing you choose `sfdc2siebaccountmigration` as domain name to trigger the use case, you just need to hit `http://sfdc2siebaccountmigration.cloudhub.io/migrateaccounts` and report will be sent to the email addresses configured.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		<![CDATA[
+ http.port `9090` 
+ page.size `100`

#### Oracle Siebel Business Objects Connector configuration
+ sieb.user `SADMIN`
+ sieb.password `SADMIN`
+ sieb.server `192.168.10.8`
+ sieb.serverName `SBA_82`
+ sieb.objectManager `EAIObjMgr_enu`
+ sieb.port `2321`
+ sieb.timeOffset=-7

#### SalesForce Connector configuration
+ sfdc.username `joan.baez@orgb`
+ sfdc.password `JoanBaez456`
+ sfdc.securityToken `ces56arl7apQs56XTddf34X`
+ sfdc.url `https://login.salesforce.com/services/Soap/u/32.0`

#### Email Details
+ mail.from `batch.migrateaccounts.migration%40mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `cesar.garcia@mulesoft.com`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job Finished Report`
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
		<![CDATA[
SalesForce imposes limits on the number of API Calls that can be made. Therefore calculating this amount may be an important factor to consider. This template uses just one query to Salesforce,
therefore this is not something to worry about.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This is the file where you will find the inbound and outbound sides of your integration app.
This template has only a [HTTP Connector](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/HTTP+Connector) as the way to trigger the use case.

$H$H# Inbound Flow
**HTTP Connector** - Start Report Generation
+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migrateaccounts` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This file holds the functional aspect of the Anypoint template, directed by one flow responsible of conducting the business logic.
For the purpose of this particular template the *mainFlow* just executes a [Batch Job](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing) which handles all its logic.
This flow has Exception Strategy that basically consists on invoking the *defaultChoiseExceptionStrategy* defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>